Register of the Pierre Lanneret Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS, 1902-1984 (Box 18)
  - Poster, n.d. (Folder 18: 7)
    Visual aid showing the locations of the artillery positions of the Paris Commune, 1871, prepared by Lanneret for a lecture on the subject of the Commune
  - Serial issues, 1902-1968.
    - Le pioupiou de l'Yonne, no. 4, 1902; no. 2, 1904 (Folder 18: 8)
    - Action, nos. 3, 5, 8-9, 11-14, 16-17, 1968. (Folder 18: 9)
      Published by the Service des Comités d'Action during the student and worker revolt in France, 1968 May-June
    - L'Express, unnumbered supplement, 1968. (Folder 18: 10)
      Special issue relating to the May 1968 revolt in France
    - France-soir, 1968 May 12-13. (Folder 18: 11)
      Special issue devoted to rioting in the Latin Quarter in Paris